Ann Cottrell Free Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Ann Cottrell Free Papers 1854-2018 1935-2000
MSS86321
Free, Ann Cottrell
101,500 items
289 containers plus 1 classified and 5 oversize
120 linear feet
343 digital files (1.66 GB)
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Journalist, author, environmentalist, and animal welfare advocate. Writings, oral history transcripts, and photographs in both physical and digital formats. Material in physical format also include correspondence, notebooks, diaries, newspaper clippings, research files, and printed matter. All primarily relate to Free’s journalistic career after 1940.
Acquisition Information
The papers of Ann Cottrell Free were given to the Library of Congress by Elissa Blake Free in 2019. Numerous additions were given by her between 2019 and 2022.
Transfers
Audiovisual items have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division. Among the transferred items are audiotapes of interviews, oral histories, conversations, and speeches by Free. Patrons are encouraged to contact the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division in advance of a research visit.
Other Repositories
Additional records related to Ann Cottrell Free's oral history conducted by Recording Animal Advocacy can be found at the Columbia Center for Oral History at Columbia University.
Related Material
Related collections in the Manuscript Division include the James Free Papers (see https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/eadmss.ms008052) and Ruby A. Black Papers (see https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/eadmss.ms010063).
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Ann Cottrell Free are open to research. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use. Access to digital content is available onsite only in the Manuscript Reading Room and requires advanced notice. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting.
National Security Classified Information
Government regulations control the use of national security classified items in this collection. Manuscript Division staff can furnish information concerning access to and use of classified material.
Technical Requirements
Digital files were created in a Windows operating system, version is unknown. The content is primarily text files in .doc and .pdf formats and image files in .jpg and .tiff formats. Files in .indb and .indd formats created in the program InDesign are not accessible. However, the text from these files is viewable in related .pdf files.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1916, June 4 Born, Richmond, Va.
1938 B.A., Barnard College, New York, N.Y.
1938 1940 Journalist, Richmond Times-Dispatch
1940 Publicist, Virginia, Paramount Pictures, Charlottesville, Va.
1940 1941 Correspondent, Newsweek, Washington bureau, Washington, D.C.
1941 1942 Correspondent, Chicago Sun, Washington bureau, Washington, D.C.
1942 1945 Correspondent, New York Herald Tribune, Washington bureau, Washington, D.C.
1943 Chair, Mrs. Roosevelt's Press Conference Association
1946 1947 Chief information officer, United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, China
1947 circa 2000 Freelance journalist
1948 1949 Information officer, Economic Cooperation Administration, Europe
1950 Married James Free (died 1996)
1963 Published Forever the Wild Mare. New York: Dodd, Mead
1963 Awarded Schweitzer Medal, Animal Welfare Institute
1976 circa 1995 Board member, Albert Schweitzer Fellowship
1982 Published Animals, Nature, and Albert Schweitzer. New York: A. Schweitzer Fellowship
1987 Published No Room, Save the Heart. Washington, D.C.: Flying Fox Press Awarded Rachel Carson Legacy Award, Rachel Carson Council
1996 Elected to the Virginia Communications Hall of Fame
2004, Oct. 30 Died, Washington, D.C.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Ann Cottrell Free (1916-2004) span the years 1854-2018, with the bulk of the material dating from 1935 to 2000. The collection documents Free’s personal life and professional career as a journalist, author, environmentalist, and animal welfare advocate. The papers are primarily in English, with French, Spanish, and Chinese. The collection is organized into eight series: Personal File, Correspondence, Speeches and Writings, Subject File, Photographs, Notebooks and Diaries, National Security Classified Information, and Oversize.
The collection focuses on both Free’s personal life and professional career. The bulk of the collection is arranged by subject and reflects file groupings and folder titles created and maintained by Free. As a result, the collection is highly interconnected with related topical files found in multiple locations within and across series. Prior to donation to the Library of Congress, Free’s daughter, Elissa Blake Free, also arranged some of the material, sometimes including personal notes to provide greater context to the files. Some personalized or unconventional folder headings were placed in quotation marks to reflect Free’s original terminology and language used throughout the collection. The collection reflects the many topics Free was passionate about and explored in her writing throughout her life. Prominent topics include animal welfare, the environment, nature, civil rights, the plight of refugees, and the empowerment of women.
The collection’s series are listed and briefly described below. A fuller description of each series and a list of its contents can be accessed in the series descriptions within the container list.
The Personal File series primarily contains biographical material that provide an overview of Free’s life and career.
The Correspondence series comprises personal and professional correspondence from Free’s family, friends, and colleagues, the bulk of which spans from 1937 to 1997.
The Speeches and Writings series comprises articles, books, short stories, speeches, and essays written by Free.
The Subject File series largely consists of working and background files that document the breadth of topics Free wrote about throughout her career.
The Photographs series comprises prints, negatives, and scrapbooks that mostly document Free, her family, her friends, and her travels in the late 1940s.
The Notebooks and Diaries series contains Free’s notebooks and diaries spanning from her college years in the late 1930s until her death in 2004.
The remaining series contain Oversize and National Security Classified Information material.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in eight series:
Personal File, 1854-2011
Correspondence, 1920-2005
Speeches and Writings, 1899-2018
Subject File, 1904-2007
Photographs, 1920-2015
Notebooks and Diaries, 1933-2004
National Security Classified Information, circa 1950
Oversize, 1920-1990
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Black, Ruby A. (Ruby Aurora), 1896-1957.; Carson, Rachel, 1907-1964.; Cody, Verna Mae Feuerhelm, approximately 1911-1957.; Cotlove, Elaine W., 1921-2020; Cottrell family.; Cottrell, Emily Blake, approximately 1889-1950. Emily Blake Cottrell papers.; Croÿ, Elisabeth, princesse de, 1921-2009.; Free family.; Free, Ann Cottrell--Relations with women.; Free, Ann Cottrell.; Free, Elissa Blake, 1955- Elissa Blake Free contextual notes.; Glasgow, Ellen, 1873-1945.; Grandin, Temple.; Hill, Lister, 1894-1984.; Hornaday, Mary J., 1906 or 1907-1982.; James, Claude, 1919-1985.; Johnson, Margaret L. 1905-1959.; Nies-Berger, Edouard.; Oudine, John A. (John Albert), 1916-2005.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Schweitzer, Albert, 1875-1965.; Stephenson, Malvina.; Stevens, Christine, 1918-2002.; Walker, Ernest P. (Ernest Pillsbury), 1891-1969.; Zhou, Enlai, 1898-1976.; Ziegler, Isabelle.
Organizations
Albert Schweitzer Fellowship.; Flying Fox Press.; Great Britain. Royal Navy. Women's Royal Naval Service (1939-1993); Marshall Plan.; Mrs. Roosevelt's Press Conference Association.; National Press Club (U.S.); Rachel Carson Council.; Society of Woman Geographers.; United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.; United States. Animal Welfare Act of 1970.; United States. Army. Women's Army Auxiliary Corps.; Washington Press Club (Washington, D.C.)
Subjects
Animal rights--Societies, etc.; Animal rights.; Animal welfare--Law and legislation--United States.; Animal welfare--Moral and ethical aspects.; Animal welfare--Societies, etc.; Animal welfare.; Civil rights.; Environmentalism.; Ethics.; Famines--China.; Green movement.; International relief--China.; Journalism--United States--Societies, etc.; Journalism.; Life.; Nature.; Reconstruction (1939-1951); Refugees.; Women journalists.; Women's rights.; World War, 1939-1945--Europe.; World War, 1939-1945--Participation, Female.; World War, 1939-1945--United States.
Places
Asia--Description and travel.; China--History--20th century.; China--Politics and government--20th century.; Europe--Description and travel.; India--Description and travel.; India--History--Partition, 1947-; Middle East--Description and travel.
Occupations
Animal rights activists.; Authors.; Environmentalists.; Journalists.
Container List
- Personal File, 1854-2011 (Box 1-9)
  The Personal File series primarily contains biographical material that provides an overview of Free’s life and career. This is largely reflected in transcripts of detailed oral history interviews with Free regarding her animal advocacy efforts, experiences as a female journalist in the 1940s, and work in China with the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration. Other biographical material includes awards, biographical sketches, articles about Free, résumés, and files related to her birth, marriage, and death. Of particular interest in the series is a file of notes and correspondence related to sessions with psychologist Elaine W. Cotlove in which Free discusses and analyzes her romantic relationships with women in the 1930s and 1940s. The series also contains material related to Free's family, mostly the papers of her mother, Emily Blake Cottrell, including correspondence, notebooks, and diaries. Free’s correspondence with her mother, however, is maintained primarily in the Correspondence series. While the series contains biographical and autobiographical material, similar files can be found throughout other series in the collection, mostly in Free's writings, diaries, and notebooks.
  Material types include résumés, transcripts, awards, certificates, clippings, business cards, correspondence, recipes, and notes. Some textual material is in digital format. The file structure of the digital content maintained as received.
  Arranged alphabetically by material type or subject.
  - Ann Cottrell Free Animal Reporting Award, National Press Club, 2005-2006 (Box 1)
  - Articles and writings mentioning Free, 1925-2008, undated, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Autobiographical writings, 1939-2002, undated (Box 1)
  - Awards (Box 1)
    - Dodd Mead Boys' Life Writing Award, Forever the Wild Mare, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
    - Miscellany, 1936, 1963-2003 (Box 1)
    - Schweitzer Medal, Animal Welfare Institute, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
    - Virginia Communications Hall of Fame, 1993-2000 (Box 1)
  - Biographical sketches, 1943-2005, undated (Box 1)
  - Biographical sketches, 1943-2005, undated, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Birth, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Blake, Emma Walters (grandmother), 1944, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Business cards, circa 1940s-circa 1990s (Box 2)
  - Contacts, circa 1940s-circa 1990s (Box 2)
  - Cotlove, Elaine W., psychiatrist, notes and letters, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Cottrell, Emily Blake (mother) (Box 2)
    - Address book, undated (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1923, 1931-1972, undated, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1923, 1931-1972, undated (Box 3)
    - Death, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Financial notes, 1965-1971, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Miscellany, 1925-1971, undated (Box 3)
    - Notebooks and diaries, 1941, 1971, undated (Box 3)
    - Notebooks and diaries, 1941, 1971, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Cottrell, Emily Blake, and Emmett D. Cottrell, (parents), 1924-1967, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Death (Box 4)
    - Condolences, 2004-2005, (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Donations, 2004-2005 (Box 5)
    - Memorial plaque, 2005 (Box 5)
    - Memorial service, National Press Club, Washington, D.C., 2004, Dec. 4, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Miscellany, 1990, 2004 (Box 5)
    - Obituaries and tributes, 2004-2005, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Education, 1923-1940, 1950-1954, 1963, 1973, 1983, 1998 See also OV 1 and OV 2, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Family, miscellany, 1903, 1983, 1997, 2002, undated (Box 5)
  - Free, James (husband), memorial service, 1996, Apr. 21 (Box 6)
  - Genealogy, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Identification and membership cards, 1933-2000 (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Mary M., and James West, wedding book, 1854-1857 (Box 6)
  - Marriage to James Free, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Mementos (Box 6)
    - Dance cards, circa 1930s (Box 6)
    - Foreign currency, 1912-1964 (Box 6)
    - Menus, 1920, 1944-1946 (Box 6)
    - Playbills and ticket stubs, circa 1940s, 1975, undated (Box 6)
    - United States presidential campaign buttons, circa 1952-1956, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Miscellany, 1942-1943, 1981, 2008, undated (Box 6)
  - Name plates, undated (Box 6)
  - Oral history transcripts (Box 6)
    - China, 1997 (Box 6)
    - "Covering World War II Washington," 1994 (Box 6)
    - National Press Club, Washington, D.C., 1992, 1998, 2004-2007 (Box 6)
    - "Personal Oral History of Ann Cottrell Free" conducted by Elissa Blake Free and Bill Nooter, 1994-2004, 2011, (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - "Personal Oral History of Ann Cottrell Free" conducted by Elissa Blake Free and Bill Nooter, digital copy, 2004, mss86321_200_056
    - Proposal, Montgomery College, Rockville, Md., 1996 (Box 7)
    - Recording Animal Advocacy (organization) (Box 7)
      - Anchel, Marjorie, oral history, 1997 (Box 7)
      - Free, Ann Cottrell, oral history (Box 7)
        - Full transcript, 2001 (Box 7)
        - Full transcript, digital copy, 2003, mss86321_200_057
        - Lee, Carmen, correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 8)
        - Miscellany, 1998-2003 (Box 8)
        - Segments I-IV, 1999-2000, (4 folders) (Box 8)
        - Supplemental material, 1996-2001, (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - "Telling Their Story is All I Can Do," 1999-2000 (Box 9)
      - Orlans, F. Barbara, oral history, 2001-2002 (Box 9)
      - Thurston, Ethel, oral history, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Washington Press Club Foundation, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Press passes, 1945-1983, undated (Box 9)
  - Recipes, 1893, 1938, 1950s-1960s (Box 9)
  - Résumés, circa 1941-circa 1990 (Box 9)
  - Travel satchel, circa 1940s See OV 1, same heading (Box OV 1)
  - Travel documents, 1948-1949, undated (Box 9)
  - War ration books, 1942-1943 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, 1920-2005 (Box 9-25)
  The Correspondence series comprises personal and professional correspondence from Free's family, friends, and colleagues, the bulk of which spans from 1937 to 1997. The correspondence is wide-ranging, touching on many aspects of Free’s life and career. Details of her travels in the 1940s are reflected within the series in letters to Emily Blake Cottrell and John Oudine, in a subject file on India, and in a compilation of letters to and from her travel companion, Verna Mae Feuerhelm Cody. Other files of note include letters related to Free’s romantic relationships with Margaret Johnson, Claude James, and Isabelle Ziegler. A file of “early job letters” reflects Free’s experiences with sexism in the journalism profession from the 1930s to 1950s. The series does not represent the entirety of correspondence in the collection as letters are filed throughout other series. Researchers are encouraged to consult the Subject File series for correspondence related to specific subjects.
  Material types include letters, memoranda, invitations, greeting cards, telegrams, faxes, postcards, photographs, and writings.
  Arranged into a chronological file, a name file, and a subject file.
  - Chronological file, 1931-1933 (Box 9)
  - Chronological file, 1934-1941, (8 folders) (Box 10)
  - Chronological file, 1942-1962, (11 folders) (Box 11)
  - Chronological file, 1963-1975, (9 folders) (Box 12)
  - Chronological file, 1976-1985, (9 folders) (Box 13)
  - Chronological file, 1986-1993, (8 folders) (Box 14)
  - Chronological file, 1994-2005, undated, (7 folders) (Box 15)
  - Chronological file, undated, (6 folders) (Box 16)
  - Name file (Box 16)
    - Allen, Thelma, 1963-1996 (Box 16)
    - Baničević, Marija, 1948-1949, undated (Box 17)
    - Black, Hugo, 1966-1971 (Box 17)
    - Bredow, Fran; Yap, Micronesia, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
    - Bush, George, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Cody, Verna Mae Feuerhelm, 1946-1961, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 17)
    - Cottrell, Emily Blake, and Emmett D. Cottrell, (parents), circa 1920s-1942, (4 folders) (Box 17)
    - Cottrell, Emily Blake, and Emmett D. Cottrell, (parents), 1943-1959, (12 folders) (Box 18)
    - Cottrell, Emily Blake, and Emmett D. Cottrell, (parents), 1961-1979, undated, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Douglas, William O., 1954 (Box 19)
    - Ellard, Roscoe, North American Newspaper Alliance, 1954-1955 (Box 19)
    - Enniskillen, Nancy, Countess of, 1943, 1961, 1991-1999 (Box 19)
    - Frederick, Pauline, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Free, James (husband), 1939-1986 (Box 19)
    - Hume, Margaret, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Garnett, R. W., 1949-1950, undated (Box 19)
    - James, Claude, 1942-1944, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1966, 1951 (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Margaret L., 1935-1937, (8 folders) (Box 20)
    - Johnson, Margaret L., 1937-1939, 1955, undated, (5 folders) (Box 21)
    - Lowenstein, Takako, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Lucie, Noel, 1948-1964 (Box 21)
    - Oudine, John, 1936-1947 (Box 21)
    - Oudine, John, 1936-2008, (7 folders) (Box 22)
    - Oudine, John, 1939-1948, undated, (4 folders) (Box 23)
    - Pryor, Roberta, 1970-1978 (Box 23)
    - Sarton, May, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Schaal, Eric, 1940 (Box 23)
    - Weckerle, Thea, 1947-1989, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Ziegler, Isabelle, 1932-1992 (Box 23)
    - Ziegler, Isabelle, 1932-1992 (Box 24)
  - Subject file (Box 24)
    - Animal concerns, 1957-1998, (4 folders) (Box 24)
    - Birthday greetings, 2004 (Box 24)
    - Early job letters, 1935-1957 (Box 24)
    - Houghton, Mifflin and Co., 1977-1980 (Box 24)
    - India, 1947 (Box 24)
    - Job applicants to work for Free, 1977 (Box 24)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., funeral, 1968 (Box 24)
    - Love letters; Manfred, Eric, 1933, 1944-1950 (Box 24)
    - Media and animals, 1954-1997 (Box 25)
    - Newspapers, publications, film, and television, 1937-2001 (Box 25)
    - United States Congress; United States Senate, 1948-1995 (Box 25)
    - White House invitations and greeting cards, 1941-2001 (Box 25)
- Speeches and Writings, 1899-2018 (Box 25-50)
  The Speeches and Writings series comprises articles, books, short stories, poems, speeches, and essays written by Free. The bulk of the writings spans from 1942 to 1999. In addition to published and unpublished writings, the files contain drafts, working files, and background on Free’s publishing company, Flying Fox Press. Files are mostly arranged by type of writing, with the exception of a group of files Free arranged by subject that include a largely unorganized mix of articles, drafts, notes, and fragments. Additional files containing both published and unpublished writings, namely Free’s writings on the Animal Welfare Act, Rachel Carson, China, the Marshall Plan, Albert Schweitzer, and Eleanor Roosevelt, can be found in the Subject File. Notable unpublished manuscripts in this series mostly focus on animal welfare topics. Free’s unpublished manuscript about her experiences in China in the 1940s and her biography of Rachel Carson can be found in the Subject File. Some writings arranged by subject also include photographs, most notably the Women's Army Auxiliary Corps and Women's Royal Navy Service files.
  Material types include articles, poems, essays, books, speeches, short stories, outlines, notes, clippings, drafts, correspondence, photographs, and advertisements. Some textual and visual material and images are in digital formats. The file structure of the digital content maintained as received.
  - Advertisements and flyers, 1985-1996 (Box 25)
  - Articles, 1935-1941 (Box 25)
  - Articles, 1942-1953, (8 folders) (Box 26)
  - Articles, 1954-1989, (8 folders) (Box 27)
  - Articles, 1990-2000, undated, (4 folders) (Box 28)
  - Books (Box 28)
    - Animals, Nature, and Albert Schweitzer (Box 28)
      - Chinese translation, 1994-1998 (Box 28)
      - Correspondence, 1976-2000, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Drafts and notes, circa 1979-1988 (Box 28)
      - Drafts and notes, circa 1979-1988, (3 folders) (Box 29)
      - Permissions, Eden Publications, 2003-2004 (Box 29)
      - Promotional materials, 1980-1990 (Box 29)
      - Published copy, 2013 (Box 29)
      - Reprint, BookCrafters, 1992-1998 (Box 29)
      - Reprint, Port City Press, 1988-1992 (Box 30)
      - Reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 30)
      - Rights and permissions, 1980-1982, 1988, 1998 (Box 30)
    - "Cruel and the Kind"; "Divided Heart," 1954-1998, (6 folders) (Box 30)
    - "Cruel and the Kind"; "Divided Heart," 1966-1998 See also OV 2, same heading, (8 folders) (Box 31)
    - "Don't Despair of Me," 1899-1900, 1950-1968 (Box 31)
    - "Don't Despair of Me," 1899-1900, 1950-1968 (Box 32)
    - Flying Fox Press (Box 32)
      - Book orders, 1982-2002, (7 folders) (Box 32)
      - Miscellany, 1986-1991 (Box 33)
    - Forever the Wild Mare (Box 33)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1998, (3 folders) (Box 33)
      - Drafts, circa 1958-1963, (3 folders) (Box 33)
      - Drafts, circa 1958-1963, (3 folders) (Box 34)
      - Galley proofs, 1963 (Box 34)
      - Miscellany, 1957-1964, 1973, 1982-1989 (Box 34)
      - Pentland Press, 1998 (Box 34)
      - Production files, 2018, mss86321_200_059
      - Promotional materials, 1963-1964 See also OV 4, same heading (Box 34)
      - Przewalski's horse, 1958-1997 (Box 35)
      - Przewalski's horse, 1958-1997 (Box 35)
      - Published copies, 1963, 2018, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Reviews, 1963-1964 (Box 35)
      - Söderbom, Georg, circa 1958 (Box 35)
    - "Meat: The End of the Affair," proposal, 1976-1981 (Box 35)
    - "Meat: The End of the Affair," proposal, 1976-1981 See also OV 2, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - No Room, Save the Heart (Box 36)
      - Book orders, 1987-1995, (3 folders) (Box 36)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - Drafts, circa 1930s-1986, (5 folders) (Box 37)
      - Miscellany, 1986-1987 (Box 37)
      - Promotional materials, 1987-2002 (Box 37)
      - Published copy, 2007 (Box 37)
      - Reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 38)
    - "Silver Spoons and One Red Apple," circa 1992-1999, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - College themes, circa 1934-1938, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Essays, 1934-1955 (Box 38)
  - Essays, 1934-1955, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Fragments of writings, circa 1934-1970, (4 folders) (Box 39)
  - Poetry, 1929-1988, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Poetry, 1930-2002, (6 folders) (Box 40)
  - Poetry, 1932-1994, undated, (11 folders) (Box 41)
  - Short stories, circa 1930s-1940s, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - Short stories, 1934-1963, (9 folders) (Box 42)
  - Short stories, 1954-1963 (Box 43)
  - Speeches, 1965-2001, (3 folders) (Box 43)
  - Subjects (Box 43)
    - American Magazine, 1951-1959 (Box 43)
    - Animals, 1935-1997, (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Animals, 1935-1997, (6 folders) (Box 44)
    - Animals, 1935-1997, (6 folders) (Box 45)
    - Animals, 1935-1997, (8 folders) (Box 46)
    - Dumplings, 1957-1958 (Box 46)